fiu.edu 2002-12-11

# FIU Internet Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Florida International University website. Your privacy is very important to us. It is our policy to collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.When you visit our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our website. This process does not result in the identification of your email address or any other personal information.

We gather information on the date, time and pages accessed by visitors to the website. This is information is compiled to improve the content and structure of our website. Only aggregate information is collected. No individual’s personal information is identified, and none of the information gathered is shared with other organizations.

If you choose to share personal information with us, by sending a message or filling out an electronic form, we will use the information only for the purposes authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with the State of Florida’s archiving policies. However, we will not disclose information about public visitors to this site with third parties or other government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law. If we are required to disclose information about you by law, we will make every effort to notify you of the disclosure in advance.

If you have questions about FIU’s Internet Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at webmaster@fiu.edu or contact us by telephone at 305.348.3849.
